漂泊者
我们不回去了，他死了！
We're not turning around. He's gone!
什么叫做“他死了”
What do you mean, "He's gone"?
他还动着呢，我他妈看着他动呢
He was still moving. I fucking saw him still moving.
我们杀人了！
We killed people!
你他妈什么意思？掉头！
What do you mean? Turn the fucking car around!
他已经死了！我们能怎么办！
He's gone! What are we supposed to do?
妈的，这破玩意不值得我把他扔在那
Damn it, this shit's not worth it for me to leave him there!
我们杀人了，哥们
We killed people, man.
老天，拜托，我求你了，他是我亲弟啊
HENRY: God damn it! Please, I'm begging you. He's my fucking brother.
我说过就可能会这样
I said this would happen.
操你妈，Archie
Fuck you, Archie!
操你妈
Fuck you!
你走到哪都得带着你兄弟
You can't go anywhere without your brother.
我头都快炸了
And I very almost got my head blown off,
因为他永远是个小孩，照顾不了自己
because he's a fucking baby who can't look after himself.
坐好了
- Fuck you!  ---Sit still!
妈了个逼的
God damn it!
所以他现在成了这样
ARCHIE: So then, now, look what happens to him.
错不在我们
Can't be feeling responsible for that.
如果他能照顾好自己
If he was a man who could look after himself,
他就该接受现在这状况
he'd be accepting it right now.
操你妈，你再说一遍
Fuck you. Say that again.
你听到我说什么了，你知道的
You heard me. You know it.
操你妈，Archie，你再说一遍
Fuck you, Archie! Say that again!
如果他是个大人，就不该哭
If he was a man, he wouldn't be crying about it,
接受那状况
he'd be accepting it.
你他妈再说一遍
Say that one more goddamn time.
我说两遍了
I said it twice.
再他妈说一遍，Archie
One more goddamn time, Archie.
再说一遍也是那样
If I said it again, I'd say it the exact same way,
再说就三遍了
and that'd be three times I said it!
走，赶紧，赶紧，赶紧
- Let's go. Come on, come on, come on.
赶紧！
Come on!
那谁啊？
Who's this?
那是我们的车，哥们。-什么？
- That's our truck, man. --- What?
妈的他想干啥？
What the fuck's he doing?
我操
Jesus, fuck!
- 他放弃了吧？ - 他不会放弃的
-  Is he giving up? - He ain't giving up.
他搞哪样
What's he doing?
他想搞哪样？
他想跟着咱们，哥们
He's gonna keep following us, man.
行，行，行
Okay, okay, okay.
开过来了
He's moving.
哥们，你想搞哪样
What's going on with you, brother?
我说你想搞哪样，哥们
I said what's going on, brother?
我要拿回我的车
I want my car back.
哦，我看出来了
Yeah, I can see that.
但你拿不回去了
You ain't gettin' it back.
我要拿回我的车
I want my car back.
如果你现在不还回来
If you don't give it to me now,
我会一直跟着你们，直到你还回来
I'm gonna get back in that truck and I'm gonna stay on you till you do.
你凭什么觉得我不会在这杀了你
What makes you think I won't kill you right here?
哈？
Huh?
不凭什么
Nothing makes me think that.
别闹了
Come on, just for a little...
需要什么服务
Do you need anything?
我在找我的车，车上有三个人
I'm looking for my car. It's got three people in it.
车没在这停
MAN: It hasn't stopped here.
他们需要汽油
They needed petrol.
我这没汽油
I haven't got any petrol.
见着我车了吗
Did you see it?
没见着一辆坐着三个人的车，你想买点别的吗
I haven't seen a car with three people in it. Do you want to buy something?
我这有啤酒，汽车配件，还有些别的
I've got tins of stuff and some auto accessories and other things.
我在找一辆车，车上有三个人
I'm looking for a car with three people in it.
你见着了吗
Have you seen it?
没有
No.
别的什么人见着了吗
Anyone else seen it?
我不知道
I don't know.
谁知道
Who would know?
奶奶可能知道
Maybe Grandma.
奶奶在哪
Where's Grandma?
里头
Down there.
我在找我的车，车上有三个人
I'm looking for my car. It's got three men in it.
从这过了吗
Did it come through here?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
你见着我车了吗
Have you seen it?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
你见着了吗
Have you seen it?
你想来点什么吗
Do you want something?
想睡小男孩吗
Do you want to sleep with a boy?
我这有小男孩可以睡
I've got a boy here you can sleep with.
又白又嫩的
He's smooth like the inside of your arm.
别他妈唧唧歪歪
COLIN: Stop fucking whispering.
我要买把枪
I need to buy a gun.
再他妈唧唧歪歪，老子宰了你俩
Stop fucking whispering.
I'll fucking kill ya.
- 明白了吗！ - 我要买把枪
- You understand? - I need a gun.
你有枪吗
ERIC: Have you got guns?
你觉得我在这干嘛
COLIN: What does it look like I'm doing up here?
我听到你说什么了
I heard you. I heard what you need.
神经病
Fucking psycho.
小心点
Careful.
300块一把，这把300块，那把300块
They're 300 each. That one's 300. That one's 300.
那把也300，我只收美元
And that one's 300.
I only take US dollars.
我没有300块
I don't have 300.
300美元一把
They're $300 US.
这把能便宜点
Can you do this one for less?
已经告你多钱了
I told you how much they cost.
我没有300块
I don't have $300 US.
300块一把，你没有300块，那你滚蛋
They're 300. You don't have 300, you can fuck off.
我在找我的车，你见着了吗
I'm looking for my car. Have you seen it?
告诉我你的名字，我想知道
Tell me your name.I want to know your name.
- 回答我的问题 - 回答我的
- Answer my question. - Answer mine.
回答我的问题，我不会再问一遍
Answer my question. I'm not gonna say it again.
好吧
Okay.
我叫你“宝贝”好了
I'll call you "my baby."
宝贝
My baby.
有一辆车
There was a car
上头有三个人，和所有的车一样
and it had three men in it and it did what most cars do.
它从一个方向开来然后开走
It came in one direction and left in the other.
我能告诉你的就是这些
That's all I can tell you about it.
我能告诉你的细节，都是关于这个地方的
The only detail I can tell you is the detail that pertains to this place.
我能告诉你他们喝了什么
I can tell you what they drank.
我能告诉你他们闻着什么味
I can tell you what they smelled like.
我能告诉你他们说了什么，如果他们说了的话
I can tell you what they said, if they said anything
如果我听到他们说了什么的话
and if I heard what it was that they said.
他们说什么了
What did they say?
他们什么也没说，他们没在这停
They didn't say anything. They didn't stop here.
你一定很喜欢那辆车，亲爱的
You must really love that car, darling.
这个时代还有什么值得兴奋的
What a thing to get worked up about in this day and age.
你为什么这么喜爱那辆车
What is it about the car
that you love so much?
你能告诉我吗
Can you tell me?
你叫什么名字，亲爱的
What's your name, sweetheart?
别傻了
Oh, don't be silly.
你只是气坏了
Now you're just being rude.
你对这车干嘛了
What are you doing with this car?
这是我哥的车
It's my brother's car.
谁是你哥
Who's your brother?
他在哪
Where is he?
Henry在哪
Where's Henry at?
谁是你哥，他在哪
Who's your brother? Where is he?
告诉我他在哪，否则杀了你
You tell me where he is, or I'm gonna kill you.
他在哪
Where is he?
这没有医生
There's no doctor here.
我应该是这个小镇最有用的人
I'm about the most useful person in this town.
当你知道离这个小镇最近的医生有多远
If that gives you any idea how far from having a doctor this town is.
别的地哪有医生
Is there a doctor somewhere else?
你买点东西
Buy something.
告诉过你我这卖什么，有啤酒有喝的有别的
I told you what I've got. I've got tins of things and drinks and stuff.
整天处理搞你这破事
I have to deal with this shit all day.
拜托
Please.
没跟你开玩笑
I'm not joking.
你怎么说“拜托”都行，但我没在开玩笑
You can say "please" all you like, but I'm not joking.
现在，从货柜上给自己挑点东西
Now, pick yourself something off the shelf.
给Benny结账
Pay Benny.
医生在山上，出门向东
There's a doctor in them hills there. Head east,
沿着朝山的路走，就到了
and follow the road that looks like it leads to those hills, you'll get there.
到那有个大黄标志，上面写着“人苠医院”
It's got a big yellow fridge out the front, says "Peeples" written on it.
兜里枪放下来
Pull the gun out of your pants.
我车里有个小孩需要救治
I've got a kid in the car who needs help.
兜里的枪掏出来，放在地上
Pull the gun out of your pants and put it on the ground.
他需要救治
He needs help.
这是你朋友吗
Is this man your friend?
医疗费多少
How much do you want for doing this?
我不需要你的钱
I don't want your money.
我过没有货币的生活过得很好
I've gotten pretty good living without money.
我必须把这些孩子养在这起来
I have to keep these guys locked up in here now for the most part,
不然人们会把它们当肉吃了
'cause people take them for food.
它们来我这
These guys came to me.
它们的主人们扔下它们
People just drop them off
说要离开一阵，让我帮忙照料
and ask me to look after them while they went away somewhere
或者说要去做别的什么事
or because they had to go somewhere or do something,
然后一去不复返
and none of them ever came back.
他们应该都是去挣钱了
I guess they've gone looking for money.
你想让我帮你看下你的伤口？
Do you want me to take a look at your cuts?
不用
No.
嘿
Hey.
感觉怎么样
How ya going?
我还行
I'm well.
嗯，愿不愿意坐下来我帮你检查看看
Um, do you wanna take a chair while I have a look at you?
疼吧
It hurts.
手拿开吧
Do you want to take your hand away?
看起来不是太糟糕
That doesn't look too bad.
看起来很好，你只需要让伤口保持干净就行了
That looks good. You just need to keep this clean.
告诉我你哥在哪
Tell me where your brother is.
我会带你去的
I'll take you to him.
告诉我你哥在哪
Tell me where your brother is.
嗯
Mmm.
他去了南边，离这很远，我会带你去的，我保证
He's gone south a long way from here.I'll take you to him, I promise.
我给你找件衣服
I'm just gonna get you a T-shirt.
起来，上路
Get up. We're leaving.
我们可能得听听那位医生小姐怎么说
Maybe we should ask what the lady says.
起来
Get up.
- 这铃响是什么意思 - 是有车过来了
- What was that sound? - It's a car coming.
什么车
What car?
我不知道
I don't know.
又一辆
That's two cars.
- 他们多快到这- 一分钟，也许
- How long till they're here? - A minute, maybe.
是谁
Who is it?
把你来福枪拿出来
Get your rifle.
- 你认识他们吗 - 把你来福枪拿出来
- DOROTHY: Do you know them? - Go and get your rifle.
告诉我发生什么事了
Tell me what's going on.
这些是什么人
Who are these people?
起来，上路
Get up. We're leaving.
起来
Get up.
我们在哪
Where are we?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
搞点吃的？
REY: Go and get some food?
现在告诉我
You're gonna start talking to me.
什么？
What?
别他妈什么什么，我们这是去哪
Don't fucking "what" me. Where are we going?
除了已经告诉你的，别的都不能说
I can't tell you nothing more than I already told you.
我不管你已经跟我说了什么
I don't give a shit what you think you've already told me.
现在就告诉我
Start fucking talking to me!
老公别这样
Don't.
你其实也不知道我们在哪是吧
Do you even know where we are?
- 什么？ - 我们在哪？
- What? - Where are we?
我们在哪
Where are we?
我不知道
I don't know.
你他妈不知道？
You don't fucking know?
那么，你怎么去想去那地
So, how are you gonna get to where you're going
如果你他妈都不知道你在哪
if you don't know where the fuck you are?
你听得懂我刚才在说什么吗，智障
Do you even understand what I just said, half-wit?
我们去Carloon
We're going to Carloon.
(帕丁森在说中文)
(这也是中文)
我刚才问那个姐姐怎么去Carloon
I just asked that lady how to get to Carloon from here.
你听得见我和她说话
I was gonna do that anyway and you would've heard me
你也可以自己去问，看看我是不是在说谎
and you would've asked her what I said, figured out what I said anyway.
不过我还是先告诉你
I was gonna tell you anyway.
情况不是很乐观
You wanna know so bad.
你不知道去了Carloon之后具体位置在哪
But you don't know exactly where in Carloon we're going exactly,
所以局面还是我在控制
so, I'm still in control here.
你不知道去了Carloon之后具体位置在哪
You don't know exactly where in Carloon we're going,
所以你得带我和你一起去
so you got to take me with you.
我会带你一起去，因为如果到了Carloon
I'm taking you with me because if I get to Carloon
你哥不在那，我会割了你的喉咙
and your brother's not there,
I'm gonna slit your throat.
为什么你那么想对我哥干坏事
What you want with my
brother so bad, hmm?
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是Rey，你是想问这个？
I'm Rey. Is that what you mean?
你为什么会在这？
Why are you here?
我和我哥从矿上出来，和其他所有人一样
Me and my brother came out for
the mines. Like everybody else.
你哥为什么在Carloon
Why's your brother in Carloon?
那是他本来要去的地方
That's where he was gonna go.
为什么你在这，而你哥在Carloon
Why are you here and your
brother's in Carloon?
他们非常着急走
They had to get going
in a big hurry.
为什么
Why?
他为什么这么着急走
Why did he have to get going in a big hurry?
我不知道，我不能说
I don't know. I can't talk about it.
为什么你个这么着急去Carloon
Why did your brother have to get to Carloon in a big hurry?
这个我不能说
I can't talk about it.
好，不管他想做什么
Well, whatever it was he did,
他就去做了，同时把你扔在这等死
you got left here to die
while he was doing it.
- 不是这样的 - 是吗
- It didn't happen like that.- Really?
那是怎样
How did it happen, then?
我不能说，快别问了
I can't talk about it no more,just stop asking about everything.
因为我相信老天爷，我哥Henry也信
'Cause I believe in God and I know Henry believes in God,
Henry不会看着我受伤不管的
and there's no harm Henry would want to see me come to.
我相信这一点
I believe in that.
那看看你肚子上那窟窿，Henry在哪呢
Yet look at the harm you've come to and where's Henry?
他在等我
He's waiting for me.
他没在等你
He's not waiting for you.
他在
Yes, he is.
没有，他没在等
No, he's not.
我来告诉你老天爷给了你什么
I'll tell you what God's given you.
他塞了个子弹进你肚子
He's put a bullet in you.
然后把你抛弃给了我，而我根本不认识你
And he's abandoned you out here
to me, who feels nothing for you.
你明天死了什么事也不会发生
I couldn't give a fuck
if you die tomorrow.
老天爷给你一个没在等你的老哥
God gave you a brother
who's not waiting for you.
给你一个现在恐怕都想不起你来的老哥
He gave you a brother who's not
even thinking about you right now.
只因为你和他是从同一个肚子里出来的所以你们是兄弟
Just because you and him came
out of the same woman's hole.
现在所有有意义的事是
The only thing that means
anything right now
我在这而他不在
is that I'm here and he's not.
你哥扔下你不管，让你去死
Your brother left you to die.
人们都在干这事
That's what people do.
你不学着去抗争，你就真的快死了
You don't learn to fight, your
death's gonna come real soon.
别开枪了！
Stop shooting!
我只是想去抗争
I just wanted to fight.
I just wanted to fight him.
我们走吧
Let's go.
走着
Come on.
那个姐姐说，过去去那要花大概8小时
That lady said it would take about eight hours to get there, in the old days.
但现在可能会更久，因为那些老路都荒废了
But it might take longer now 'cause a lot of them old roads ain't there no more.
现在路都很烂，你开不快
And all the roads are bad now anyways
so you can't drive fast on 'em.
她说可能要8或者9个小时
She said about eight or nine hours.
她不确定是8小时还是9小时
She wasn't sure if it was eight or nine.
她很不确定
She seemed a bit confused about it.
那你哥为什么还在那
And why would he still be there?
他在那呆两个星期等人
He had to wait two weeks for someone.
他在那有个人要见，要等两个星期
There's a man there he's got to meet, it's gonna take two weeks.
你确定是这样，还是他告诉你的
You know this? Or this is what he told you?
哈？
Huh?
你哥那人不能信
Your brother can't be trusted.
这事是“你知道”还是“他告诉你的”
Is this something that you know or is this something that he told you?
都是
Both those things.
你在矿上工作？
You work in the mines?
不
No.
那你是做什么工作？
What do you do then?
我过去种田，现在我在这
I was a farmer. And now I'm here.
那你从哪学得枪，枪法这么好
Then how come you learned how to shoot so good?
你以前当兵的吧？
You was in the army?
我小时候在一个农场长大
When I was a little kid I grew up on a farm.
我们的邻居，Verna和Clarry，老到不行
We had these neighbors, real old
man and lady, Verna and Clarry,
他们是兄妹
they's brother and sister.
他们的田里全是荒草
And they lived on this
land that's all overgrown,
你都说不出来他们在种什么，全被荒草淹没了
like you couldn't even tell what
they farmed, so overgrown.
Clarry有8台拖拉机，没有一台是正常工作的
And Clarry had these eight tractors,
and none of them worked properly,
每天早上他都把所有的拖拉机放下山，直到其中有一台开始启动
so every morning he'd roll each one down
the hill till he got one of them started
然后用能启动这台把别的拖拉机拖回来
and then use that one to tow all
the others back up.
他每天都这样
He did that every day.
我们从来没有见过他们家人，他们死后
And when they died, their family,
who we'd never met before,
他们的家人四处赶来，声称继承他们的房子
came around, cleared
out their house
最后他们发现
and they found all this...
他们发现许多奇怪的玩意
They found all this weird stuff in there.
比如
Like...
比如50 therm
Like 50 therm...
热力电台阀门
Thermionic radio valves.
他们用在老收音机上的老阀门
Like them real old valves
they used in old radios.
还有南瓜金字塔
And pyramid of pumpkins.
还有大概5000个这样稀奇古怪的玩意
And about 5,000 of these
little sticks about this long.
每个都用报纸包着，用绳子挂起来
And each wrapped up in newspaper and
tied up at the ends with baling twine.
你为什么跟我说这些
Why are you telling me this?
我只是记起来了
I just remembered it.
觉得很有趣
It interested me.
不是什么事都必须意味着什么嘛
Not everything has to be about something.
我试着不去想那个死去的女孩，但我控制不住
I'm tryin' to stop thinking about
that little girl who died, but I can't.
别
You shouldn't.
可我控制不住
But I can't.
你别控制，是你该想的
You shouldn't stop thinking about her.
你应该永远记得这个被你带走的生命
You should never stop thinking
about a life you've taken.
这是你该承受的代价
It's the price you pay for taking it.
就是这样，骚逼
That's it, sweetheart.
从睁开眼睛开始
Let's start with the eyelids.
趴过去，手放在背后
I want you to roll over onto your
front, put your hands behind your back.
慢慢做
And do it slow.
现在做！
And do it now.
你啥时候才开口说话，婊子
SOLDIER: When are you gonna say something, cunt?
完蛋了
It's over.
你完蛋了
It's over for you.
我知道
I know that.
很好，你知道
That's good that you know that.
你也知道吗
Do you know it, too?
哦，我知道，小哥
Oh, I know it, champ.
跟你说了
I told you it.
你知道你也完蛋了吗
Do you know it's over for you, too?
你说我完蛋，我早就完蛋了
Whatever you think's over for
me was over a long time ago.
那你呢
I'm asking about you.
你是在威胁我妈
Are you threatening me?
不是
No.
威胁意味着什么事将会发生
A threat means there's still something left to happen.
你想怎么处置我
What are you gonna do with me?
你会被送去悉尼
You're going to Sydney.
为什么不直接枪决我
Why don't you just shoot me?
为什么不这样
Why don't you do it?
别人都是这么做的
That's what everyone else is doing.
因为我会把你送去悉尼
Because me sending you to Sydney
告诉他们我们在认真努力的工作，给我们发薪
tells Sydney there's a reason to
keep paying us what they pay us.
如果我们简单地枪决每个我们想枪决的傻逼
If we just shot every
idiot we wanted to shoot,
那很快，他们会疑惑我们在这荒山野岭做什么
then pretty soon they'd start to wonder
what the fuck we're doing out here.
所以说，我个人不在乎你怎么样
See, personally I don't care about you.
我不在乎你去不去悉尼，去了又被放了
I don't care if you get to Sydney and they
let you off or you bribe your way out
或者你靠贿赂出来怎么地，最近就是这样
or whatever the fuck they
do down there these days.
我完全不在乎
I don't give a fuck.
我这样做是为自己
I'm doing this for me.
你在为自己做什么
You're doing what for you?
我杀了自己媳妇
I murdered my wife.
我跟踪她去了一个男人家里
I followed her to a man's house,
这个男的把手伸进我媳妇裙子里，我杀了他俩
I watched him put his fingers
inside her and I killed 'em both.
没有人来找过我
No one ever came after me.
十年前的事
Ten years ago.
我从来没向任何人解释过我的感受
I never had to explain myself.
我从来没有因为这件事撒过谎
也从来没有因为这件事逃亡或躲避
I never had to lie to anyone.
I never had to run and hide.
我只是把他们埋了然后回家
I just buried 'em in a
hole and I went home.
没有人来找过我
No one ever came after me.
而这比我媳妇出轨还让我难受
And that hurt me more than
getting my heart broken.
知道这没关系
Knowing it didn't matter.
知道你可以杀掉两个人而没有人会找上你
Knowing you can do something like
that and no one comes after you.
你做了一件和我一样的事，这应该以为着什么
You do a thing like I did, that
should really mean something.
但这一切都没有意义
But it just doesn't matter anymore.
啊，小哥
Well, champ.
你在Abo镇做的事，对我们来说确实是有“意义”的
Thing you did in Abo town is the
one thing that does matter to us.
现在你可以“撒谎”或者“认罪”了
Now you can do all the lying
and confessing you'd like.
你早上醒来的时候感觉怎么样
What feeling do you have when
you wake up in the morning?
当你的脚踏上地板
When your feet touch the floor?
或在那之前，你躺在床上，想象你的脚踏上地板
Or before that, when you're lying there
thinking about your feet hitting the floor.
你感觉怎么样
What does that feel like for you?
你知道我在说什么吗
Do you know what I'm talking about?
不知道啊，小哥，我不知道
No, mate. I don't.
你不知道？
You don't?
不知道，小哥。我不知道你他妈在说什么。
No, mate. I don't know what
the fuck you're talking about.
怎么回事
MAN: What the fuck?
咻
Phew!
就这样？
Is that it?
这么容易？
That was easy.
我用不用再射他一发确认一下
Do I shoot him again just to be sure?
不用
No.
嗯
Mmm.
太简单了，总共才三个人
That was easy. There were only three of 'em.
本来还以为会困难点
Thought it was gonna be way more harder.
你绑着呢？
You tied up?
我偷偷杀了这两个
I snuck up on these two.
他俩刚在这聊着呢
They were just hanging there.
我从那边门进来的
I came through the gate there.
我在围墙底下挖了个洞，可以从这滑出来
I dug a hole out. Slipped underneath the fence.
车在那边
Get the truck over there.
走着，老哥
Come on, man.
你想换我开会车吗
You want me to drive for a while?
不用
No.
我喜欢坐在一个人旁边，不说话
I know I feel comfortable with someone
when I can just sit, not talking to them.
嗯啊
Yeah.
我喜欢只是坐着，不说话
I just like sitting there, not talking.
我就感觉坐着很舒服，你知道
I just feel comfortable sittin' there, you know.
我这边伤口真得很疼哎
I had a pain in my side real bad.
疼得厉害啊
It's starting to hurt.
我可能得怎么弄一下
I think maybe I gotta do something with it.
看起来不糟吧
Don't look bad?
把绷带盖回去
Let's put that bandage back on.
感觉不太妙啊，老哥
I think it broke, man.
有汽油吗
You got any fuel?
50美元
MAN: 50 US.
50澳币
50 Australian.
只收美元
MAN: US dollars.
我没有美元
I'm out of US.
我只收美元
MAN: I only take American money.
澳币怎么不能用了
What's wrong with Australian money?
要买掏钱，不买拉倒
MAN: Either take it or leave it.
它只是纸，没有价值
It's paper. It's worthless.
啊，随你说，哥们，我无所谓
Yeah, whatever, mate, I don't care.
他妈就是一张纸
It's a piece of fucking paper!
要买就买，不买拉倒
Take it or leave it.
多钱啊，哥们
How much you need, man?
50美元
MAN: 50 US.
你卖0.38毫米子弹吗
Have you got any .38 in there?
卖
Yeah.
给我来一盒
Let me get a box of that.
给我这位朋友来一盒9毫米的
And a box of 9 millimeter for my friend here.
多谢
Thank you kindly.
这就是那房子
REY: There's the house.
别的都是空的
All them others empty.
没人住了
They ain't got people in them anymore.
就只有他们在那吗
Are they alone in there?
现在只有他们
For now they are.
直到下礼拜有人来
Until them other people come, but that ain't
gonna be for another week or somethin'.
Gordon也在那，是他的房子，他已经很老了
And there's Gordon, whose house it is, but he's old.
非常老
Real old.
你“知道”？
Do you know this?
我知道
I know it.
我们到早晨再去
We'll go there in the morning.
早晨麻烦不那么多
There'll be less trouble.
我要去杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
我要去杀了Henry
I'm going to kill Henry.
睡觉去
Go to sleep.
他们那还有钱，我们需要就可以拿
There's money up there too,
we can take if we want.
睡觉
Go to sleep.
你搞哪样
What you doing?
在这等着
Just wait there.
他们在睡觉
They're asleep.
里屋有俩，我去拿下
There's two in the back room. I'll take them.
侧屋也有俩
There's two in the room on the other side.
你拿下侧屋那俩，把他们带到前门这房间
If you take them, we'll bring them into this front room.
行吗？但别开枪
Okay? But no shooting.
好的
All right
别说话
Don't say a word.
把头慢慢从枕头上移开
Slowly lift your head off the pillow.
你搞毛
What the fuck?
毯子踢掉
Kick your blanket off.
你们两个都起来
Both of you get up.
Henry.
Henry，起来
Henry, wake up.
Rey?
你起来
You gotta get up.
Rey，你搞毛
Rey, what the fuck?
你也起来，Gordon.
You too, Gordon.
你起来，你俩都从床上下来
You gotta get up. You both gotta get up outta bed.
你搞哪样，别用那东西对着我
What are you doing? Stop pointing that thing at me.
别让我一直重复，你俩起来
Don't make me keep saying it.
You got to get up out of bed.
坐下，坐
Sit down. Sit.
手放在屁股下
Sit on your hands.
里面怎么回事
What's going on in there?
看到了吧，Henry
See, Henry?
你从床上下来
You gotta get up outta bed.
Rey，谁在外面
Rey, who's in there?
他不起来
He won't get up outta bed.
把枪放下，Rey
Put the gun down, Rey.
你把的你枪放下
You put yours down.
Rey，把枪放下，我认真的
Rey, put the gun down.
I ain't playing.
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
你为什么把我扔在那
Why did you leave me there?
把你扔在哪？
Leave you where?
你知道在哪，马路边，我中枪了
You know where. On the road, when I was shot.
Rey，我们以为你死了
Rey, we thought you was dead.
没
No.
我没死，但你把我扔在那了
But I wasn't. But I wasn't dead and you left me there.
Rey，我以为你死了，现在把枪放下！
Rey, I thought you was dead. Now put down the fucking gun!
你把你枪放下
You put yours down.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我想尿尿
I gotta piss.
你他妈动动试试
Don't you fuckin' move.
我还以为你是我哥
I thought you was my brother, man.
我天，Rey，我是你哥，现在把那逼枪放下
God damn it, Rey! I am your brother. Now put down the fuckin' gun.
我以为你是我哥
I thought you was my brother.
Rey，你不把枪放下我就要开枪了
Rey, if you don't put down the gun I'm gonna shoot you.
行吗，我不是开玩笑的
All right? I ain't lyin'.
你本来该是我哥，Henry，你跟爸说
You was supposed to be my brother, Henry. You told Pa.
Rey，放下那逼枪！
Rey, put down the goddamn gun!
我以为你是我哥结果你把我扔在那
I thought you was my brother and you just left me there.
里面什么情况
What's going on in there?
你对我弟做了什么？
What did you do to my brother?
啊？
Huh?
回答我
Answer me.
你对我弟做了什么？
What did you do to my brother?
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything.
你做了
Yes, you did.
你对他做了什么？
What did you do to him?